Subscribe to the BankBazaar.com
channel and press the bell button
to watch the video first Hello friends,
welcome to our YouTube channel
BankBazaar.com Friends, if you are interested in
removing the cover photo then
watch this video carefully In this video
we will tell you
important information related to that bank account Friends, today we will
tell you that to subscribe to an ICICI Bank account you must have the
mobile application downloaded on your mobile If it is
not downloaded then I have given the
link in the description,
download the mobile application instead and activate it
So see, we have downloaded this application
and from here we will log in
and after that
see our mobile application has opened After this
you will see that there is a service option at the bottom, by
clicking there you will go to check service
And after that you will see the
indicator option here, you will click on this indicator
And after that from here you
can submit your cheque request As if
we clicked on it, you will see the
account number at the top So
enter your account number here And
after that it is asking for your address below So if
you  If you want to get a communication address, then you can
fill that address or any alternate address and click on the submit button.
As soon as you submit, your request will be
successfully registered here. If
you liked this video, then like it
and subscribe to this channel.
If you need any information related to your ICC Bank account, then
you
can comment or you
can mail us. We have given the mail ID
in the description.
Thank you friends.
[Music]